the following content is provided under a Creative Commons license
以下内容是根据Creative Commons授权提供
your support will help MIT OpenCourseWare continue to offer
您的支持将有助于麻省理工学院开放式课程继续报价
high-quality educational resources for free
免费优质教育资源
to make a donation or view additional materials from hundreds of them IT
进行捐赠或查看附加材料由数百人资讯
courses
课程
visit MIT OpenCourseWare at 0 CW
参观麻省理工学院开放式课程在0 CW
that MIT that EDU Horan
麻省理工学院的EDU霍兰
the
该
the in
在该
in
the
该
are in
在
for in discussing the sampling theorem
在讨论采样定理
we saw date for a ban limited signal which is sampled
我们看到日期为采样禁令限制信号
at a frequency that that is at least twice the highest frequency
其频率至少是两倍的最高频率
we can implement exact reconstruction
我们可以实现精确重建
of the original signal by low-pass filtering
通过低通滤波的原始信号的
an impulse train whose areas are identical to the sample values
一个脉冲串，其区域是相同的样本值
well essentially this low pass filtering
以及基本上这个低通滤波
operation provides for us and interpolation
操作为我们提供了和插值
in between the sample values in other words the output to the low-pass filter
在换句话说，样本值之间的输出到低通滤波器
in fact
其实
is a continuous curve which
是一个连续的曲线，该曲线
fits between a sample values some continuous function
一个采样值之间符合一些连续函数
now I'm sure that many have you are familiar with other kinds of
现在我敢肯定，很多你所熟悉的其他种类的
interpolation that we could potentially provide
插值，我们可能提供
in between sample values and in fact in today's lecture
在样本值，而事实上在今天的讲座之间
why I would like to do is first the ball
为什么我会想要做的是第一球
develop the interpretation
发展的解释
all the reconstruction as an interpolation process
所有重建作为插值过程
and then also see how this
然后还看不出这
exact interpolation using a low-pass filter
使用一个低通滤波器精确插值
relates to other kinds of interpolation
涉及到其他类型的插值
such as linear interpolation that you may already be familiar with
比如，你可能已经熟悉的线性插值
well to begin let's again review
好，开始让我们再次回顾
what the overall system is for exact reconstruction
整个系统是用于精确重建
sampling and reconstruction and so let me remind you that
采样和重构等等，让我提醒你，
the overall system for sampling and D sampling a reconstruction is as i
采样和D采样重建整个系统是为我
indicate here
在此说明
the sampling process consists love
采样过程由爱
multiplying by an impulse train and then the reconstruction process
由一个脉冲串，然后重建过程相乘
corresponds the processing that impulse train with
对应的脉冲串的处理
a low-pass filter so if the
一个低通滤波器，所以，如果
spectrum of the original signal
原始信号的频谱
is what I indicate in this diagram
是我指出此图
then after sampling with an impulse train
然后用脉冲序列采样后
that spectrum is replicated and
频谱被复制，
this replicated spectrum for reconstruction
这个复制的光谱重建
is then processed through a low-pass filter
然后，通过低通滤波器处理
and so in fact if this frequency response
因此，事实上，如果该频率响应
is an idea low-pass filter as i indicated on the diagram below
是一个想法的低通滤波器正如我下面的图上
then multiplying the
然后乘以
spectrum of the sample signal by this extracts 4s
该采样信号的频谱提取4S
just the portion all
只是部分全部
the spectrum centered around the origin
围绕原点为中心的频谱
and what we're left with then is the
而我们留下了那么什么是
spectrum finally of the reconstructed signal
重构信号的频谱终于
which for the case of an idea low-pass filter
这对于一个想法的低通滤波器的情况下
is exactly equal to the spectrum of the original signal
正好等于原始信号的频谱
now that is the
既然是
frequency domain picture
频域图片
all the sampling and reconstruction let's also look at
所有的采样和重建，让我们也看看
basically the same process but let's examine it now
基本上是相同的过程，但让我们来看看它现在
in the time domain well in the time domain
在时域以及在时域
what we have is are original signal
我们所拥有的是原始信号
multiply it by an impulse train and
由一个脉冲串乘以它和
this then is the sampled
这便是采样
signal or the impulse train whose areas are equal to the sample values
信号或脉冲串，其面积相等的采样值
and because it the fact that this is an impulse train
并且，因为它的事实，这是一个脉冲串
in fact we can take this term
其实我们可以把这个词
inside the summation
求和内
and of course what counts about except Ian this expression
当然，除了什么伊恩计算这个表达式
is just as bad use at the sampling instants
同样糟糕的使用在采样时刻
which are displaced in time by capital T and so
它由大写字母T是流离失所的时间等
to what we can to quietly right is the
要什么，我们可以静静地权是
expression for the impulse train samples or
对于脉冲串的样品或表达式
imposed strain of samples as i've indicated here
样品施加应变，因为我已经在这里表示
simply an imposed strain whose areas are the sample bad
简单地强加应变的领域是不好的范例
now in the reconstruction we process
现在我们处理的重建
that impulse train with a low-pass filter that's the basic notion of the
该脉冲串的低通滤波器，是的基本概念
reconstruction
重建
and so in the time domain be reconstructed signal
因此在时域中是重构信号
is related to the imposed strain of samples
是与样品所施加的应变
through a convolution with the filter impulse response
通过与滤波器的脉冲响应的卷积
and carrying out this convolution since
而开展这项自卷积
this is just the train of pulses in effect what happens in this convolution
这是脉冲刚刚生效的列车在此卷积发生了什么
is dead this impulse response gets
死了这个脉冲响应得到
reproduced at each of the locations 0
再生在每个位置0的
the impulses index a PFD with the appropriate area
冲动指数PFD与适当的区域
and finally then in the time domain the reconstructed signal
最后再在时域重构信号
is simply a linear combination
是一个简单的线性组合
love shifted versions of the impulse response
爱移位脉冲响应的版本
with amplitudes Witcher the sample values
与振幅巫师的样本值
and so this expression in fact and is our basic
所以实际上这表达的是我们的基本
reconstruction expression in the time domain
在时域重建表达
well in terms of a diagram
以及在图的形式
we can think of the original waveform
我们可以认为原来的波形
as I've shown here and
因为我已经在这里显示和
the red arrows denote be
红色箭头表示被
sampled waveform or the train
采样的波形或火车
love impulses whose amplitude are
爱冲动的幅度是
the sample values up the original
样本值高达原始
continuous-time signal and
连续时间信号和
then I've shown here it what might be a typical impulse response
那么我在这里表明，它可能是什么一个典型的脉冲响应
particularly typical in the case where we're talking about reconstruction with
在我们谈论重建的情况下特别典型
an ideal 0 pass filter
一个理想的0通滤波器
now what happens in the reconstruction
现在在重建会发生什么
is that the convolution love these
是卷积喜欢这些
impulses with this impulse response
冲动与此脉冲响应
means that in the reconstruction
也就是说，在重建
we superimpose wanted these impulse responses whatever the filter IPO's
我们想要叠加这些脉冲响应任何过滤器首次公开招股
response happens to be
响应恰好是
at each of these time instants and in doing that
在每个这些时间瞬间的和在这样做
then those are added up and that gives us the total reconstructed signal
那么这些被累加起来，这使我们的总重建信号
of course for the case in which the filter is an ideal
当然对的情况下，其中，过滤器是一种理想的
low-pass filter then what we know is that in that case
低通滤波器那么我们所知道的是，在这种情况下，
the impulse response is on the form of a sync function
的脉冲响应是一个同步函数的形式对
but generally we may want to consider other kinds of impulse responses and so
但是一般我们可能要考虑其他类型的脉冲响应等
in fact
其实
the interpolating impulse response
内插脉冲响应
may have and will have is this discussion goes along some different
可能有，将有是本次讨论随之而来的一些不同
shapes
形状
now what I'd like to do is illustrator demonstrate this process
现在我想要做的是插画演示这个过程
love all affectively doing the interpolation
爱所有的情感上做插值
by replacing each of the impulses
通过更换每个冲动
by an appropriate interpolating impulse response and adding the stop
通过适当的内插脉冲响应和添加的停止
and I'd like to do this with a computer movie that we generated
我想与大家产生了计算机的电影做到这一点
and what you're seeing the computer movie is
和你看到的计算机的电影是什么
essentially original way for which is a continuous curve
对于这实质上原始的方法是一连续的曲线
and then below that in the movie
然后下面，在电影
is a train samples
是一个训练样本
and then below that will be the reconstructed signal and the
然后下面，将重构信号与
reconstruction
重建
will be carried out by showing the location of the impulse response as it
将被进行了示出，因为它的脉冲响应的位置
moves along in the way form
在表格的方式一起移动
and then the reconstructed kurt is simply the summation of those is that
然后将重构的库尔特仅仅是那些的总和是
impulse response moves along
脉冲响应一起移动
so what you'll see then is an impulse response like this for the particular
所以你会看到那么就是这样的脉冲响应为特定的
case
案
love and idea low-pass filter for the reconstruction
爱情和想法的低通滤波器，用于灾后重建
an impulse response like this place
喜欢这个地方的脉冲响应
successively at the locations love
先后在爱的位置
these impulses and that is the convolution process
这些冲动，那就是卷积过程
and below that then will be the summation if these
而低于然后将总和，如果这些
and the summation up those will then be the reconstructed signal
和求和了那些随后将重构信号
so let's take a look at first of all that reconstruction
所以让我们来看看首先是重建
where the impulse response corresponds to the impulse response
其中的脉冲响应对应的脉冲响应
have an idea low-pass filter shown here first
在这里显示一个想法，低通滤波器第一
is the continuous-time signal which
是连续时间信号，该信号
we want to sample and then reconstruct using
我们要样品，然后利用重构
fan limited interpolation or equivalently
风机有限插值或等价
idea low-pass filtering on the set of samples
该组样品的构思的低通滤波
so the first step then is the sample this continuous time signal
所以第一步则是样本这种连续时间信号
and we see here now the set of samples
我们在这里看到现在的样本集
and superimposed on the samples are the original continuous 5 signal
和叠放在样品上是原始的连续5个信号
to focus on the fact that those are samples are the top curve
专注于一个事实，即这些是样品的顶部曲线
let's now remove the continuous-time
现在让我们去掉连续时间
envelope with the samples and it's this set of samples that we then want to use
信封的样本，它的这组样品的，我们当时想用
for the reconstruction
对于重建
the reconstruction process interpreted as interpolation
重建过程解释为插值
consists of replacing each sample with a sin x over X function
包括与赎罪x在X功能替换每个样品
and so let's first consider the sample
所以，让我们首先考虑样本
at equal 0 and here is the
在同等0这里是
interpolating sin x over X function Associated
插值罪倍过相关X功能
with that sample now the more general
与该样本现在更普遍的
process then is to
过程则是
place a sin x over expulsion at the time location of each sample and superimpose
放置一个罪恶x在驱逐在每个样本的时间位置和叠加
those
那些
let's begin that process at the left-hand and
让我们开始这一进程在左侧和
the set of samples and in the bottom curve
该组样品，并在底部曲线
will build up the reconstruction as those sin x over X functions
将建立重建那些罪恶倍过x形式的函数
are added together so we begin with the left hand sample and we see their the
合在一起，我们开始用左手样本，我们看到了他们的
sin x over X function
罪倍过X功能
on the bottom curve then is the first step in the reconstruction
底部曲线上则是在重建的第一步
we now have the sin x over X function associated with the second sample
我们现在有罪过x在与第二样本关联X功能
let's add that in now we move on
让我们补充一点，在现在我们继续前进
to the third sample and that sin x over X function
第三样品和罪x在X功能
is added in
在加
continuing on the next
继续对下一个
sample generates a sin x over X function
示例生成一种罪过x在X功能
which is superimposed on the result that we've accumulated
这是叠加在我们已经积累的结果
so far and now let's just
到目前为止，现在就让我们
speed up the process will move on to the fifth sample
加快这一进程将进入到第五个样品
add that in the sect sample add that in
补充说，该教派样品中添加的
and continue on through the set of samples and
并继续通过样本集与
keep in mind the fact that basically what we're doing explicitly here
记住，基本上我们在做什么，在这里明确的事实
is the convolution up the impulse train with a sin x over X function
是卷积起来的冲动列车赎罪x在X功能
and because the set of samples that we started with
并且，因为我们开始与样本集
where samples haven't exactly been limited function
其中样品已经不完全受到了限制功能
what we are reconstructing exactly
我们现在正是重建
is the original continuous-time signal
是原来的连续时间信号
that we have on the top trace
我们对顶部曲线
okay so that then
好吧，让当时
kinda gives you the picture above doing
还挺给你做上面的图片
interpolation by replacing the impulses by a continuous curve and that's the way
插值由一条连续的曲线取代了冲动，这就是方式
we're fitting
我们正在装修
a continuous curve to the original
一条连续的曲线为原始
impulse train and let me stress
脉冲串，让我压力
that this reconstruction process
这个重建过程
by putting the impulses through
通过把冲动通过
a filter the reconstruction process
一个过滤重建进程
follows this relationship whether or not
如下这种关系是否
this impulse response in fact corresponds to an ideal ok pass filter
其实这种脉冲响应对应于一个理想的确定通滤波器
what this expression always says is dead reconstructing this way
这是什么表情总是说死了重建这种方式
corresponds to replacing the impulses
对应更换冲动
by a shift in impulse response with an effort to
通过在脉冲响应的移位与努力
dead is an amplitude corresponding to the sample value now
死是对应于采样值现在的振幅
be kinda reconstruction dead we've just talked about and the ideal
是有点死重建我们刚才谈到的理想
reconstruction
重建
is often referred to as band limited
常被称为带限
interpolation because for interpolating in between the samples
内插，因为样品之间进行内插在
by making the assumption that the signals ban limited
通过使假定的信号禁止有限
and using the impulse response for an idea low-pass filter
以及使用脉冲响应为一个想法的低通滤波器
which has a cutoff frequency consistent with
其中有一个截止频率具有一致的
the soon band with for the signal so if we look
即将与乐队的信号，所以如果我们看
here for example at the impulse train
在这里，例如在列车冲动
then in the demonstration that you just saw
那么，你刚才看到的演示
we built up the reconstructed curve by replacing each of these impulses
我们建立了重建的曲线，通过更换这些冲动
with the sync function and the some of those
与同步功能和其中一些
built up the reconstruct the curve well
建立了重建曲线以及
there are lots of other kinds of interpolation
还有很多其他种插值的
dead are perhaps maybe not as exact
死也许，也许不是确切
by often easier to implement and what I'd like to do is focus our attention on
通过经常更容易实现，什么我想要做的就是集中我们的注意力放在
to appease
安抚
one of these the first that I want to mention is what's referred to as a
其中之一是我首先要提到的是什么被称为
zero-order hold
零阶保持
where in effect we do the interpolation in between these
那里实际上我们做的插值在这些之间
sample values by simply holding the sample value
简单地举行了样本值的样本值
until the next sampling instant and the reconstruction
直到下一个采样时刻和重建
that we end up with in that that case will look something like this:
我们结束了在这种情况下，将看起来像这样：
it's a staircase or boxcar kinda function
这是一个楼梯或棚车还挺功能
where we've simply held the sample value
在那里，我们已经简单地举行的样本值
until the next sampling instant and then replaced by that value held until the
直到下一个采样时刻，然后由该值取代一直保持到
next sampling instant et cetera
下一个采样时刻等等
now that's one kinda interpolation
现在这是1还挺插值
another kinda very common interpolation is
另一个有点很常见的插值
what's referred to as linear interpolation we simply fit
什么是称为线性插值，我们只是配合
a straight line between the sample values and in that case
样本值之间的和在这种情况下，一个直线
the cut be type reconstruction that we would get
切是类型重建，我们会得到
would look something like I indicate here where we take a sample value
看起来像我在此表明，我们采取的样本值
and the following sample value and simply fit interpolated curve between
而下面的示例值，简单地之间的拟合曲线插值
them
他们
which is a straight line now
这是一条直线现
interestingly in fact both the zero-order hold
有趣的是，事实上无论是零阶保持
and the linear interpolation which is
以及线性内插是
often referred to as a first-order hold can also
通常被称为一阶保持也可以
be either implemented or interpreted both implemented interpreted
被实施或解释执行两种解释
in the context of the equation that we just develop
在我们刚刚发展方程的背景下
in particular the processing I'll the
特别是处理我会的
imposed strain of samples by
样品施加应变由
a linear time-invariant filter specifically
一个线性时不变滤波器专
if we consider a
如果我们考虑一个
system where the impulse response
系统中的脉冲响应
is a rectangular function
是矩形函数
then in fact if
那么实际上，如果
we processed the train if samples
我们处理的列车，如果样本
through a filter with this impulse response exactly
通过与此脉冲响应的滤波器恰好
the reconstruction that we would get is what I've shown here
我们会得到的重建是我在这里显示
alternatively if we chose an impulse response
相反，如果我们选择的脉冲响应
which was a triangular
这是一个三角形的
impulse response then
脉冲响应则
what in effect happens is that each of these impulses
实际上发生的事情是这些冲动
activates this triangle
激活这个三角形
and when we add up those triangles at successive locations in fact
而当我们添加了这些三角形在实际上连续位置
what we generate is this linear interpolation
我们生成这是什么线性插值
so what this says in fact is dead
所以这行，其实是死的
either a zero-order hold
无论是零阶保持
which holds the value or linear interpolation
它保存的值或线性内插
can likewise be interpreted as a process
同样可以被理解为一个过程
love convolved thing the impulse trainer samples
爱卷积东西的冲动训练样本
with inappropriate filter impulse response
用不恰当的滤波器的脉冲响应
well what I'd like to do is demonstrate
还有就是我想要做的就是证明
as we did with the ban limit interpolation or
当我们与禁限插或做
these sink interpolation is sometimes called interplay with a sin x over axe
这些接收器插有时也被称为相互作用与赎罪倍过斧
let me now show the process first the ball
现在让我第一次显示进程球
where we have a zero-order hold
在这里我们有一个零阶保持
as corresponding to this impulse response
作为对应于该脉冲响应
in which case we'll see basically the same process as we saw your
在这种情况下，我们会看到基本上是相同的过程，因为我们看到了你的
in the computer-generated movie previously
在先前的计算机生成的电影
but now rather than a sync function replacing
但现在，而不是同步功能替换
each of these impulses will have a rectangular function
每个脉冲将具有矩形函数
that will generate then are approximation which is a zero-order hold
这将产生然后是逼近这是一个零阶保持
and following that will do exactly the same thing with the same way form
而下面会做同样的事情用同样的方式形式
using a first-order hold or a triangular impulse response
使用第一阶保持或三角形脉冲响应
in which case well we'll see again is that as the triangle moves along here
在这种情况下，以及我们将再次看到的是，作为三角形沿移动这里
and we build up the running some or the convolution
我们建立运行一些或卷积
then will in fact fit the original curve
那么，实际上是在配合原有的曲线
with a linear curve soul now let's
用线性曲线的灵魂现在让我们来
again look at that remembering that at the top will see
再看看那个回忆，在上方会看到
the original continuous curve exactly the one that we had before
原来连续的曲线正是一个我们以前有
below it the set of samples together with
它下面的样本集与
the impulse response moving along and then finally below that
脉冲响应沿，然后移动终于低于
the accumulation of those impulse responses work with only
这些脉冲响应的积累与只能工作
the convolution or equivalent Lee the reconstruction
卷积或同等利重建
so we have the same continuous-time signal that we use previously with
因此，我们有我们以前使用的相同的连续时间信号
ban limited interpolation and in this case
禁止有限插补并且在这种情况
now we want to sample and then interpolate first for the zero-order
现在我们要样品，然后先插的零阶
hold
持有
and then with the first-order whole so the first step then
然后用一阶全是这样，那么第一步
is the sample the continuous-time signal
是样品的连续时间信号
and we show here at the set of samples once again
我们在这里展示的样本集再次
superimposed on which we have the continuous-time signal
叠加在其上我们有连续时间信号
which of course is exactly the same curve as
这当然是完全一样的曲线作为
we have in the top well let's
我们在上面也让我们
remove that envelope so that we focus attention
删除信封，让我们把注意力集中
on the samples that were using to interpolate
上的是用内插样本
any interpolation process consists love replacing each sample
任何插值过程由爱替换每个样品
by a rectangular signal
由矩形信号
whose amplitude is equal to the sample size
其幅度等于样本大小
so let's put one first of all at equal 0 Associated
所以让我们把所有的一个首先在平等0美联社
with that sample
与样品
and that then would be the interpolating rectangle associated with the sample at
并且然后将与样品在相关联的内插矩形
equal 0
等于0
now to build up the interpolation what will have is one of those that each
现在建立起来的插值什么将是那些每一个
sample time and those are
采样时间和那些
added together will start that process as we did before
加在一起将开始这一进程，因为我们以前那样
at the left hand and that the set of samples
在左手和该组样品
and build the interpolating signal on the bottom so
并建立在底部的内插信号，使得
with the left hand sample we have first
用左手示例中，我们首先有
the rectangle associated with that that shown
这表明与该关联矩形
now on the bottom curve we now
现在底部的曲线上我们现在
have a senator plating rectangle with the second
与第二参议员电镀矩形
sample that gets headed into the bottom curve
样品会越走越一进入底部曲线
similarly and interpolating rectangle for the zero-order hold
类似地与内插矩形的零阶保持
with the third sample we had bad in to the bottom curve
与第三个示例中，我们在底部曲线有坏
and as we proceed we're building a staircase approximation
当我们继续我们正在构建一个阶梯近似
on to the next sample that gets added in
上会越走越中添加的下一个样本
as we see the air and now lets speed up the process
因为我们看到了空中，现在可以加快进程
and we'll see the staircase approximation
我们将看到楼梯逼近
building up and notice in this case
建立并通知在这种情况下，
as in the previous case that what we're basically watching dynamically
在什么我们基本上动态看前面的情况
is the convolution love the imposed strain of samples
被卷积爱样品所施加的应变
with the impulse response the interpolating filter
用脉冲响应内插滤波器
which in this particular case is just a rectangular Paul's
在这种特定的情况下，仅仅是一个长方形的保罗
and so this staircase approximation that we're generating
所以这个阶梯近似，我们正在生成
is the zero-order hold interpolation
是零阶保持插值
between the samples I love the
样本之间我爱
ban limited signal which is at the top
禁止有限信号，它是在顶部
now let's do the same thing with the first-order whole so in this case
现在让我们做同样的事情与一阶全所以在这种情况下，
we want to interpolate using a triangular impulse response
我们想用一个三角形的脉冲响应进行内插
rather than the sin x over X or rectangular impulse responses that we
而不是罪x在X或矩形脉冲响应我们
showed previously
以前发现
so first let's say with the sample it equals 0
所以首先让我们说与它等于0的样本
we would replace that with a triangular
我们将取代有一个三角形
interpolating function and more generally
内插函数和更一般地
each in polls or sample is replaced with a triangular
在每个轮询或样本被替换为一个三角
interpolating function of the height equal to the sample height
高度等于采样高度的插值函数
and these are superposed to generate the linear interpolation
和这些被叠加，以产生线性内插
will begin this process with the leftmost
将开始这个过程，最左边的
sample and will build the superposition
采样和将建成的叠加
below and the bottom curve so here
下方和底部的曲线所以在这里
is the interpolating triangle for the
是内插三角形的
leftmost sample and now it's reproduced below
最左边的样本，现在它的下面转载
with the second sample we have an interpolating triangle which is added
与第二示例中，我们有其中加入内插三角
into the bottom
进入底部
curve and now on to the third sample
曲线和现在第三样品
and again that interpolating triangle will be added onto
并再次强调插三角形将被添加到
the curve that we've developed so far
我们到目前为止已经开发了曲线
and now on to the next sample
现在到下一个样本
we had that in there will speed up the process
我们必须在那里将加快进程
and as we proceed through
而当我们通过
we are building basically a linear interpolation
我们正在建设基本上是一个线性插值
in between the sample points
在采样点之间
a sexually corresponding to if one wants to think of it this way connecting the
一种性对应，如果一个人想想起来这种方式连接
dots
点
and what you're watching once again is essentially the convolution process
和你看一次什么本质的卷积过程
involving the impulse train with the impulse response
涉及的脉冲列的脉冲响应
the interpolating filter and what we're generating then
插值滤波器和我们正在生成然后
is a linear approximation
是一个线性近似
to the fam limited continuous-time curve at the top
到顶部的FAM有限的连续时间曲线
okay so what we have then is
好了，我们有什么，然后是
several other kinds of interpolation which
其他几种插值的这
fit within the same context as
符合相同的上下文中
exact ban limit interpolation one being
确切的禁令限制插值的一个是
interpolation in the time domain with an impulse response which is a rectangle
插在其中是一个矩形脉冲响应的时域
the second being interpolation in the time domain
第二个是插在时域
with an impulse response which is a triangle
用这是一个三角形的脉冲响应
and in fact its interesting to also
而事实上它的有趣也
look at the relationship between at and ban limit interpolation
看在和禁限插值之间的关系
look at it specifically in the frequency domain
看它专门在频域
well in the frequency-domain
以及在所述频域
what we know of course is dead for exact interpolation
我们当然知道什么是死亡的确切插值
what we want as our interpolating filter is an ideal Lopez filter
我们要为我们的插值滤波器什么是理想的洛佩兹过滤器
now keep in mind by the way that an idea low-pass filter is an abstraction is a
现在牢记的方式，一个想法的低通滤波器是一种抽象为一个
stress several times in the past an idea low-pass filter
强调多次在过去一个想法的低通滤波器
is a9 causal filter and in fact infinite extent which is
是A9因果滤波器，实际上无限的程度是
one of the reasons why in any case we would you some approximation to it
的原因，在任何情况下，我们将您的一些逼近它的一个
but here what we have is the
但在这里我们所拥有的是
exact interpolating filter
确切的插值滤波器
and that corresponds to an ideal 0 pass filter
以及对应于理想的0通滤波器
if instead we carried out the interpolation
相反，如果我们进行了插值
using the zero-order hold the zero-order hold has a
使用零阶保持在零阶保持有
rectangular impulse response and that means in the frequency domain
矩形脉冲响应，这意味着在频域
its frequency response is of the form love
它的频率响应是形式的爱
a sync function or sin x over iraq's
同步功能或罪恶倍过伊拉克
and so this in fact when we're doing the reconstruction
所以这实际上当我们正在做的重建
with a zero-order hold is The Associated frequency response
用零阶保持是相关联的频率响应
now notice that it does some approximate Lopez filtering but of course
现在发现，它确实有些近似洛佩兹的过滤，但当然
it has significant it permits significant energy
它具有显著它允许显著能源
outside the pass band at the filter
在滤波器的通带外
well instead the zero-order hold if we use the first-order hold corresponding
以及代替零阶保持，如果我们使用相应的第一阶保持
to the triangular impulse response
于三角形脉冲响应
in that case then in the frequency domain The Associated
在这种情况下，然后在频域中的相关
frequency response would be the forty a transformer the triangle
频率响应将是40变压器的三角形
and the Fourier transform a triangle is a sin squared
和傅立叶变换的三角形是一个平方罪
X over X where'd kinda function
X的基于X哪儿还挺功能
and so in that case what we would have
所以在这种情况下，我们将有
for the frequency response associated with the first-order hold
用于与第一阶保持相关联的频率响应
is a frequency response as I show here
是的频率响应，因为我在这里展示
and the fact dead that there's somewhat more attenuation
而事实上死了还有较为衰减
outside the pass band at the ideal filter
在理想的滤波器的通带外
is what suggests in fact dead the first-order hold or linear interpolation
是什么建议，其实死一阶保持或线性插值
gives us a somewhat smoother approximation to the original
给了我们一个比较平滑的近似原
signal then the zero-order hold does
信号然后在零阶保持不
and so in fact just to compare these two
所以实际上只是为了比较这两个
we can see that here is
我们可以看到，这里是
the ideal filter here is
这里是一个理想滤波器
the zero-order hold corresponding to
的零阶保持对应于
generating a boxcar kinda reconstruction
产生棚车还挺重建
and here is the first order hold corresponding to a linear interpolation
这里是对应于线性插值的第一阶保持
now in fact in many sampling systems
现在其实很多采样系统
in any sampling system really we need to use some approximation
在任何采样系统真的，我们需要使用一些近似
to the low-pass filter and very often in fact
到低通滤波器，而且往往实际上
what is done in many sampling systems is the first to use
什么在许多采样系统做的是首先使用
just a zero-order hold and then follow the zero-order hold
只是一个零阶保持，然后按照零阶保持
with some additional 0 pass filtering
有一些额外的0通滤波
well to illustrate some with these ideas
很好地说明了一些与这些想法
and the notion love doing reconstruction
和概念爱做重建
with a zero-order hold a first-order hold and then in fact
与零阶保持一阶保持，实际上
are ending to that some additional 0 pass filtering
正在结束到一些额外的0通滤波
what I'd like to do is is demonstrator illustrate
我想要做的是为演示说明
sampling and interpolation in the context love some images
采样和插值的背景下，喜欢一些影像
image of course is a two-dimensional signal the
当然，图像是二维信号的
the independent variables are spatial variables not time variables
独立变量空间变量并不时变量
and of course we can sample in both or the spatial dimensions both in X&Y
当然，我们可以在两个或空间维度无论是在X和Y样
and were chosen as so
并同时获选为使
a possibly appropriate choice for
一个可能是合适的选择
an image is again our friend and colleague JBJ 48
图像又是我们的朋友和同事JBJ 48
so let's begin with the original image which we then
所以让我们开始与原始图像，我们再
want to sample and reconstruct and a sampling is done by
要采样和重建以及采样是通过完成
effectively multiplying by appalls both horizontally and vertically
由惊恐有效地相乘水平和垂直方向
the sample picture is then the next one
示例图片，然后下一个
that I show and as you can see this corresponds in effect
我和展示，你可以看到，这相当于生效
to extracting small brightness elements I did the original image in fact
以提取小分子的亮度我做其实原始图像
let's look in a little closer and what you can see essentially is that
让我们来看看在一点点接近，哪些是你可以看到基本上是
well we have of course tonight impulses spatially but
以及我们当然今晚的冲动，但空间
small spatial pillars dead
小空间的柱子死
implement the sampling for us okay now
实施抽样我们现在没事​​了
going back to the original sample picture
回到原来的样本图像
we know that a picture can be reconstructed by low-pass filtering from
我们知道，一个图象可以通过低通滤波从重构
the samples and in fact
样品和实际上
we can do that optically in this case by simply d focusing the camera
我们可以通过简单的Ð对焦相机做，光在这种情况下，
and when we do that what happens is that we smear out the picture
而当我们这样做会发生什么事是我们涂抹出来的图片
or affectively convolved the impulses with the point spread function of the
或情感上的卷积与冲动的点扩散函数
optical system
光学系统
an this then is not too bad a reconstruction
在这则不算太差重建
so thats a an approximate reconstruction and focusing back now
所以那是一个近似的重建和重点返现
what we have again is the sample picture
我们再有就是样品图片
now these images are in fact a can often of
现在这些图像实际上是一个可以经常的
a computer display and a common procedure in
计算机显示器和一个通用程序
computer-generated are displayed image is is in fact
计算机生成的显示图像，其实是
the use of a zero-order hold and if the sampling rate is high enough
使用零阶保持的，如果采样率是足够高的
then that actually works reasonably well so now
那么，实际工作得相当好现在这样
let's look at the result of applying a zero-order hold
让我们来看看应用零阶保持的结果
to the sampled image that I
到采样图像，我
just showed
只是表明
the zero-order hold corresponds to replacing the impulses by
的零阶保持对应于通过更换脉冲
rectangles and you can see that what that generates
矩形，你可以看到什么，产生
is a mosaic affect as you would
是你将一个镶嵌影响
expect and in fact let's going a little closer and
期望而事实上，让我们去一点点接近并
emphasize the mosaic affect you can see that essentially where they were
强调马赛克影响可以看到，基本上他们在那里
impulses previously
以前的冲动
there are now rectangles with those brightness values
现在有矩形与亮度值
a very common procedure with computer-generated images is the first
用计算机生成的图像非常常见的程序是第一
20 order holders we've done here
我们在这里所做的20阶持有人
and then follow that with some additional ok pass filtering and in fact
然后按照一些额外ok了通滤波，事实上
we can do that low pass filtering now again by D focusing the camera
我们可以用D现在再做一次低通滤波对焦相机
and you can't begin to see
你不能开始看
dead with the zero-order all plus the low-pass filtering the reconstruction is
死与零阶都加上低通滤波的重建
not that bad
没有那么糟糕
well let's go back to the full
好，让我们回到全
image with the zero-order hold
图像的零阶保持
and again now the effective low pass filter I will be
而现在又有效的低通滤波器，我会
somewhat better and let's tee focus again year
有些更好，让我们重点开球又一年
and you can begin to see that this is
你可以开始看到这是
a reasonable reconstruction with the mosaic
一个合理的重建与马赛克
in fact with this back in focus you can
其实这回的重点，你可以
apply your own low-pass filtering to it either by squinting
应用自己的低通滤波，以它要么眯眼
or if you have the right or wrong kind of my classes either taking them off for
或者如果你要么学他们的正确或错误的那种我班
putting them on
把它们放在
now in addition to the zero-order hold weekend of course apply a first-order
现在除了课程的零阶保持周末将第一阶
hold and that would
持有并会
correspond to replacing the impulses instead of with rectangles as we have
对应于与矩形取代的冲动，而不是因为我们有
here
这里
replacing them with triangles an
与三角形替换它们的
so now let's take a look at the result all a first-order hold applied to the
所以现在让我们来看看结果应用到所有一阶保持
original samples
原始样本
and you can see now that the reconstruction is somewhat smoother
你现在可以看到，重建是有点更顺畅
because the fact that we're using an impulse response
因为我们使用的脉冲响应的事实
that somewhat smoother or a corresponding frequency response that
该稍微平滑的或相应的频率响应
has a sharper cut off
有一个更清晰的切断
i emphasize again that this is a somewhat low pass filtered version of
我再次强调，这是一个有点低通滤波
the original because
原来是因为
we have under sampled some what spatially
我们已经在一些采样空间是什么
to bring out the point that I want to illustrate
带出，我想说明的一点
okay to emphasize these effects
还好强调这些影响
even more what I'd like to do is go through
更是我想要做的是通过
basically the same sequence again but in this case what we'll do
再次基本上相同的序列，但在这种情况下，我们会做
is double the sample spacing both horizontal horizontally and vertically
是双采样间距横向水平和垂直两个
this of course means there will be even more highly under sampled been
当然，这意味着将会有更多的高采样下了
in the ones that I preview show previously showed and so the result of
在那些我预览显示以前发现和这样的结果
the reconstructions with some low pass filtering
与某些低通滤波的重构
will be a much more low-pass filtered image
将是一个更低通滤波后的图像
so we now have the sample picture but I've now under sampled considerably
所以我们现在有样品图片，但现在下采样大大我已经
more and you can see the effect of the sampling
更多，你可以看到采样的效果
and if we now apply is zero-order hold
如果我们现在采用的是零阶保持
to this picture we will again get a mosaic and lets
这个图片，我们将再次获得一个镶嵌，让
look at that and that mosaic of course looks
看那个，当然容貌，马赛克
even block here than the original and again emphasizes the fact that the
甚至阻断这里比原来并再次强调一个事实，即
zero-order hold
零阶保持
simply corresponds to filling in squares or replacing the impulses
简单地对应于填充正方形或更换冲动
by squares with the corresponding brightness
由平方与相应的亮度
values finally if we instead of a zero-order hold
值最后，如果我们不是一个零阶保持
use a first-order hold corresponding to two-dimensional triangles in places
使用对应于二维三角形的地方的第一阶保持
in place at these original blocks what we get is
在参加这些原始块就是我们得到的是
the next image and that again is a smoother reconstruction consistent with
接下来的图像和又是一个平滑的重建与一致
the fact that the triangles are smoother than the rectangles
一个事实，即三角形比矩形更平滑的
again i emphasize that this looks so highly low-pass filtered
我再次强调，这看起来如此高的低通滤波
because of the fact that we've under sampled so severely
因为事实上，我们已经在采样如此严重
to essentially emphasize the effect
从根本上增强效果
as I mentioned the images that we
正如我所提到的图像，我们
just looked at were taken from a computer although
只是看着是从一台电脑，虽然
because the original images were continuous-time
因为原始图像是连续时间
images or more specifically continuous space that is the independent variable
图像或者更具体地连续的空间，它是独立变量
is a spatial variable
是空间变量
now computer processing
现在计算机处理
love signals pictures speech or whatever the signals are
恋爱讯号图片演说或其他的信号
is very important and useful because
是非常重要和有用的，因为
it offers a lot of flexibility and in fact the kinds of things that I showed
它提供了很大的灵活性，而事实上这样的东西，我表现
these pictures
这些图片
would have been very hard to do without
本来很难做到不
in fact doing computer processing
其实做计算机处理
well in computer processing %uh any kind of signal
以及计算机处理％呃任何一种信号
basically what's required is dead
基本上是什么需要的是死了
we do the processing in the context of discrete-time signals and discrete-time
我们所做的处理中的离散时间信号与离散时间的上下文
processing
处理
because it the fact dead a computer is run off the clock
因为它其实死一台计算机上运行关闭时钟
and essentially things happen in the computer
而且基本上事情发生在电脑
in a as a sequence of numbers and as a sequence of events
在作为数字序列，并作为事件顺序
well it turns out dead the sampling theorem in fact as i've indicated
还有原来死其实是采样定理，因为我已经指示
previously
先前
provides us with a very nice mechanism
为我们提供了一个非常好的机制
for converting are continuous-time signals
用于变换为连续时间信号
into discrete-time signals for example for computer processing
入计算机处理，例如离散时间信号
or in fact if it's not a computer for some other kind of discrete-time or
或者在事实上，如果它不是一台电脑供一些其他类型的离散时间或
perhaps digital processing
也许数字处理
well the basic idea as i've indicated previously
还有我以前指出的基本思路
is to carry out discreet I processing
是进行谨慎的处理工作
of continuous-time signals by
通过连续时间信号
first converting the continuous-time signal
首先将连续时间信号
to a discrete-time signal carry out
一个离散时间信号进行
the appropriate discrete-time processing
适当的离散时间处理
love the discrete-time signal and then after we're done with that process
爱的离散时间信号，然后经过我们与该进程完成
saying
话
converting from the discrete-time sequence
从离散时间序列变换
back to a continuous-time signal
返回到连续时间信号
corresponding to the output that we have here
对应于我们这里的输出
well in the remainder this lecture what I'd like to analyze
以及在其余本次讲座是什么，我想分析
is the first step in that process namely the conversion
在这个过程中的第一步，即转换
from a continuous-time signal to a discrete-time signal
从连续时间信号的离散时间信号
and understand how the
并了解
to relate both in the time domain in the frequency domain
以在频域时域涉及两
and in the next lecture will be analyzing and demonstrating
并在下一讲将分析和展示
the overall system including some intermediate processing
包括一些中间处理系统的整体
so be first step in the process
所以在这个过程中的第一步
is the conversion from a continuous-time signal
是从一个连续时间信号的转换
to a discrete-time signal and that can be thought of as a process that involves
到一个离散时间信号和可以被看作是一个过程，涉及
two steps although in practical terms it may not be implemented specifically
两个步骤虽然在实际上它可能并不是专门实施
as these two steps the two steps are
因为这两个步骤的两个步骤是
to first convert from the continuous-time
首先从连续时间转换
for continuous-time continuous signal
在连续时间连续信号
to an impulse train through a sampling process
通过一个采样过程的脉冲串
and then to convert
然后转换
that impulse train to a discrete-time sequence
冲动火车到离散时间序列
and the discrete-time sequence exit then
和离散时间序列退出然后
is simply then a sequence a bad news
只是那么一个序列的坏消息
which are the samples all the continuous-time signal
这是所有样本的连续时间信号
and as we'll see as we walk through this basically this step
正如我们将看到，我们通过这个基本上这一步走
going from the impulse train to the sequence
从脉冲串持续到序列
corresponds principally to worry labeling staff where
对应主要担心贴标工作人员在那里
we pic of the impulse bad news
我们PIC冲动坏消息
and use those as the sequence values
和使用它们作为序列值
up for the discrete-time signal so
向上的离散时间信号，以便
what I'd like to do as a first step in understanding this process
我想要做的是了解这个过程的第一步
is to analyze it in particular with our attention focused on trying to
是分析它特别是与我们的注意力集中在努力
understand
明白
what the relationship is in the frequency domain
的关系是在频域中什么
between the discrete-time Fourier transform
离散时间傅里叶变换之间
love the sequence discrete-time signal
爱序列离散时间信号
and the continuous-time 48 transform
和连续时间48变换
love the original on sampled and then
爱情原来的采样，然后
the sampled signal so let's go through that
采样信号让我们来研究研究
and in particular
尤其
what we have is a process where the continuous-time signal
我们所拥有的是一个过程，其中的连续时间信号
is of course modulator multiplied
当然是调制器的相乘
by an impulse train and that gives us then
由一个脉冲串并，让我们再
another continuous-time signal we're still in the continuous time domain
另一种连续时间信号我们仍然在连续时间域
it gives us another continuous-time signal which is an impulse train
它为我们提供了另一种连续时间信号是一个脉冲串
and in fact we've gone through this analysis
而事实上，我们通过这个分析已经走了
previously and what we have is
以前和我们所拥有的是
this multiplication or taking this term inside
这个乘法或服用此期限内
the summation and recognizing that the impulse train
求和并认识到脉冲串
is is simply an impulse train
是仅仅是一个脉冲串
with areas above the impulses which
与上面的冲动领域的
are the samples above the continuous-time function
是上面的连续时间函数的样本
we can then carry out the analysis in the frequency domain
然后就可以进行分析的频域
now in the time domain we have a multiplication process so in the
现在在时域中，我们有一个乘法处理，以便在
frequency domain
频域
we have a convolution above the Fourier transform
我们有上面的傅立叶变换卷积
love the continuous-time signal the original signal
爱的连续时间信号的原始信号
and the Fourier transform of the impulse train which is itself an impulse train
和傅立叶的冲动列车本身就是一个脉冲串变换
so in the frequency domain then the 48 transform
这样在频域，然后在48变换
of the sampled signal which is an impulse train
采样的信号是一个脉冲串的
is the convolution %uh the Fourier transform up the sampling
被卷积％呃傅里叶变换了取样
function PFT and the Fourier transform of the sampled signal
功能PFT和傅立叶变换的采样信号的
since the sampling signal is a periodic imposed strain
由于采样信号是一个周期所施加应变
its Fourier transform is an impulse train
它的傅里叶变换是一种冲动的火车
and consequently carrying out this convolution
因此开展这项卷积
in effect says that this for EA transform
实际上说，这对EA变换
simply gets replicated at each of the locations of these impulses
只需在每个这些冲动的位置被复制
and finally what we end up with an
最后我们结束了一个
is a 48 transform after
在经过48变换
the sampling process which is
采样过程是
the original for EA transform love the continuous
原为EA变换爱情的连续
signal but and it to itself
信号，但它本身
shifted by integer multiples
通过整数倍转移
above the sampling frequency and so this is the basic equation then
以上的采样频率，因此这是基本方程，然后
that tells us in the frequency domain what happens
这告诉我们在频域上发生了什么
through the first part all this two-step process
通过第一部分的所有这两个步骤的过程
now I emphasize that is a two-step process the first process
现在我强调的是一个两步过程的第一种方法
is sampling where we're still essentially
是采样的地方，我们仍然基本上
in the continuous-time world the next step
在连续时间世界下一步骤
is essentially a relabeling process
本质上是一个重新贴标签的过程
where we convert that impulse train simply to a sequence
在这里我们将其转换脉冲串干脆来个序列
so let's look at the next step
所以让我们来看看下一步
the next step is to take the impulse train and converted
下一步就是要把冲动火车和转换
through a process to sequence
通过一个过程来顺序
and the sequence values are simply then
与该序列的值是简单地再
samples 0 the original continuous signal
样品0原始连续信号
and so now we
所以现在我们
can analyze this and what we want to relate
可以分析这一点，我们要与
is the discrete-time Fourier transform
是离散时间傅立叶变换
love this and the continuous 540 a transformer
爱这和连续540变压器
this or in fact that continues type for a transformer affects up to you
这其实还是一直延续型变压器会影响到你
safety okay
安全性好
well we have the imposed strain
以及我们所施加的应变
and its Fourier transform we can
及其傅立叶变换，我们可以
get by simply evaluating for EA transform
通过简单地评价为EA变换得到
and since the Fourier transform love this
而且由于傅里叶变换爱这个
since this corresponds to an impulse train the 48 transformed by the time we
因为这相当于一个脉冲串的48转的时候，我们
change them something in it rolls
改变他们的东西在里面卷
will then have this in paul's replace
届时将有这个在保罗的更换
524 e a transformer the shift in polls
524邮箱变压器移位民调
which is this exponential factor so this expression
这是该指数因子使这个表达式
is before a transformer the impulse train
是变压器的冲动火车前
the continuous time Fourier transform and alternatively
连续时间傅里叶变换和替代地
we can look at the Fourier transform all
我们可以看看傅立叶变换所有
the sequence and this of course is
当然，该序列，这是
a discrete-time Fourier transform
离散时间傅立叶变换
so we have the continuous time Fourier transform the imposed strain
所以我们有连续时间傅里叶变换所施加的应变
we have the discrete-time Fourier transform the sequence
我们也离散时间傅里叶变换的顺序
and now we want to look at how those to relate
现在我们要看看如何对这些关系
well it pretty much falls out of just comparing these two summations
以及它几乎掉出来只是比较这两个求和
in particular this term and this term
特别是这个学期，这学期
are identical that's just the relabeling
是相同的，这仅仅是重新贴标签
Nov all what the sequence values are
十一月的所有序列值是什么
and notice that when we compare these exponential factors
并请注意，当我们比较这些指数的因素
they're identical as long as we associate capital Omega
他们是相同的，只要我们联想资本欧米茄
with little or may get times capital T in other words
很少或可能得到的时间大写字母T，换句话说
if we were to replace here capital may go by a little Omega
如果我们要在这里代替资金可能会受一点欧米茄
times capital T and replace exhibition
次大写字母T和替换展
by excessive see a venti in this expression
过多的看到在这个表达式中的通气
would be identical to this expression
将等同于该表达式
so in fact these two are equal
所以实际上这两个是相等的
where a relabeling or with the transformation between small Megan
其中一个重贴标签或小梅根之间的转​​换
capital make
资本化妆
and so in fact then the relationship that we have
所以其实当时我们有关系
is that the discrete-time Fourier transform are
是离散时间傅里叶变换是
the sequence of samples
样本序列
is equal to the continuous time Fourier transform
等于连续时间傅立叶变换
all the impulse strain of samples
全部样本的冲动应变
where we associate the continuous-time frequency variable
在这里我们将连续时间频率变量关联
and the discrete-time pic script frequency variable through
并通过离散时间图片脚本频率可变
a frequency scaling as i indicate here or said another way
一个频率调节，因为我在此说明或者说另一种方式
the discrete-time spectrum is the continuous I spectrum of the samples
离散时间谱对样品的连续余频谱
with capital mate with small Omega replaced by capital Omega
资本队友小欧米茄以资本代替欧米茄
divided by capital T
由大写字母T分
fight so we have then this two-step process
拼所以我们那么这两个步骤的过程
the first step is taking the continuous-time signal
第一步走的连续时间信号
sampling with it sampling it with an impulse train
它与脉冲串取样抽检它
in the frequency domain that corresponds to
在对应于频域中的
replicating the four EA transform
复制这四个EA变换
all the original continuous-time signals
所有原来的连续时间信号
the second step is relabeling Matt
第二个步骤是重新标记马特
in effect turning it into a sequence and what that does in the frequency domain
实际上把它变成一个序列和什么一样在频域
is provide us
是为我们提供
with a rescaling if the frequency axis or as we'll see
与重新调整，如果在频率轴上或正如我们将看到
a frequency normalization which is associated with the corresponding time
这是与相应的时间相关联的频率归一化
normalization
正常化
in the time domain well let's look at
在时域以及让我们来看看
those statements a little more specifically
这些陈述稍微更具体
when I show here it is the original continuous-time signal
当我告诉这里是原来的连续时间信号
and then below it is
然后它下面是
the sampled signal and these two
采样信号和这两个
are signals in the continuous-time domain
是信号在连续时间域
now what is the conversion from this impulse train
现在是什么从这个脉冲串转换
to a sequence well it simply taking
一个序列以及它简单地把
these in polls areas are bad news the sample values
这些民调领域是坏消息的样本值
and relabeling them in effect is a show below
和重新标记它们实际上是低于秀
relabeling them as sequence values
重新标记他们为序列值
and essentially I'm now replacing
而且基本上我现在更换
the impulse by the designation of a sequence value
的脉冲通过一序列的值的指定
that's one step but the other important step to focus on
这一步，​​但把重点放在其他重要一步
is dead whereas in the impulse trainees impulses are spaced
是死的，而在冲动学员冲动间隔
by integer multiples of the sampling period capital T
由采样周期大写字母T的整数倍
in the sequence of course because if the way that we
当然，该序列中，因为如果我们的方式
label sequences these are always space by
标签序列这些总是空间
simply integer multiples of 1
1简单的整数倍
so in effect you could say that the step in going from here
所以实际上你可以说，从这里走的步
to hear corresponds to normalizing out in the time domain
听到对应于时域中的归一化输出
the sampling period capital T
采样周期大写字母T
to stress that another way if the sampling period were doubled
要强调的是另一种方式，如果采样周期增加一倍
so there'd in this picture this spacing stretched out by a factor of two
所以想在这张图片中这个间距伸出了两个因素
nevertheless in the discrete-time
尽管如此，在离散时间
for the discrete-time signal the spacing would remain as one
对于离散时间信号的间隔将保持为一体
and essentially its the
而且基本上它的
envelope of those sequence values
包络的那些序列值的
that would then get contracts compressed in time
这将然后得到合同压缩时间
so you can think all the step in going from the impulse train to the samples
所以你可以把从脉冲串去的样品全部步骤
as a sexually a time normalization
作为一种性时间正常化
now let's look at this in the frequency domain in the frequency domain
现在让我们来看看这个在频域频域
what we have is the Fourier transform of our original continuous
我们所拥有的是我们​​原来的连续傅立叶变换
signal after sampling with an impulse train
用脉冲串采样后的信号
this spectrum retains its shape
这个频谱保持其形状
him but is replicated at integer multiples of the sampling frequency to
他，但被复制在采样频率的整数倍来
pry over capital T
撬过大写字母T
as i indicated here now
正如我现在在这里
we know that a discrete-time spectrum
我们知道，一个离散时间的频谱
must be periodic and frequency with a period of two pi
必须定期和频率为期PI
here we have the periodicity but it's not periodic with period have to pry
在这里我们有周期性，但它不是周期性的，周期要撬
its periodic with period which is equal to the sampling frequency
其周期性的，周期等于采样频率
however in converting from the samples
然而，在从样品转换
to the sequence values and we go through another step
到序列的价值观和我们经历的另一步
what the other step the other step is a time normalization
何其它步骤的其它步骤是一个时间归一化
where we take the impulses which your space by the sampling period
我们采取的冲动，你的空间采样周期
and we rescale at essentially in the time domain
我们在基本上重新定标在时域
to a space in which is unity so we're dividing out
一个空间中，是团结，我们划分出
in the time domain by a
在由时域
by a factor which is
通过一个因子是
equal to the sampling period well
等于采样周期以及
dividing out in the time domain by
在时域中划分出由
capital T would correspond to
大写字母T将对应
multiplying in the frequency domain the frequency axis by capital T and indeed
在频率轴上乘以在频域中由大写字母T和确
what happens is dead in going from the imposed strain
会发生什么是死在从所施加的应变准备
to the sequence values we now rescale
该序列值，我们现在重新调整
this axis so that in fact
该轴，使得实际上
the axis gets stretched by capital T
轴得到由大写字母T拉伸
and the frequency which corresponded to 2pi over capital T
它相当于2PI在大写字母T的频率
now gets re normalized 22 part
现在得到重新归一化的部分22
so just looking at this again and perhaps with the overall picture
所以只是看着这又或许与整体画面
in the time domain we've gone from a continuous curve
在时域，我们已经从一个连续的曲线消失了
two samples relabel those and in effect implemented a time normalization
两个样本重新标记那些和有效实施的时间正常化
correspondingly in the frequency domain we
相应地在频域中我们
have replicated the spectrum through the initial sampling process
已通过初步抽样过程复制的频谱
and then rescale the frequency axis
然后重新调整频率轴
so that in fact now this periodicity
所以，现在实际上这个周期
corresponds to a periodicity here which is to Popeye
对应于此处的周期也就是波比亚
and here which is the sampling frequency
并且这里它是采样频率
so very often in fact and will be doing this next time
所以很多时候其实并会做这种下一次
very often when you think
当你觉得很多时候
love continuous-time signals which have been converted to discrete-time signals
爱已转化为离散时间信号连续时间信号
when you look at the discrete-time frequency axis
当你在离散时间频率轴
the frequency to pie is Associated
频率来馅饼关联
with the sampling frequency
与采样频率
as it will it was applied to the original continuous-time signals
因为这将它应用到原始的连续时间信号
now as i indicated what will want to go on to from here
现在，正如我究竟会想要去从这里
is understanding I'll
为了解我会
what happens when we take a continuous-time signal
当我们把一个连续时间信号发生了什么
converted to a discrete-time signal as I just going through
转换为离散时间信号，因为我刚刚经历
do some discreet I processing with the linear time-invariant system
做一些谨慎的我处理的线性时不变系统
and then carry that back into the continuous-time world
然后携带回连续时间的世界
that is a procedure that will go through and
这是一个过程，将通过与
analyze and in fact illustrate in some detail
分析和实际上示出了某些细节
next time in preparation for that
在准备下一次
what I would be eager to encourage you to do
我会迫不及待地鼓励你这样做
using the study guide and in reviewing this lecture
用学习指导和审查本次讲座
is to begin the next lecture
是开始下一讲
with a careful and thorough understanding love
用细心和透彻的了解爱
the arguments that I just going through in particular
我只是通过特别的参数
understanding the process that's involved in going from a continuous-time
理解的涉及从连续时间持续的过程
signal
信号
through sampling to a discrete-time signal
通过采样到一个离散时间信号
and what that means in the frequency domain interns to taking the original
而这意味着什么在频域实习生服用原
spectrum
光谱
replicating it because if the sampling process
复制它，因为如果采样过程
and then sry scaling that so that
然后SRY标定，使
the periodicity gets rescaled so that its periodic
的周期被重新调整，使得其周期
with a period of two part so will continue with that next time focusing
用了一段两部分，以便将继续下一次聚焦
now
现在
on the subsequent steps
在随后的步骤
in the process thank you
在这个过程中谢谢